by RentAnAdviser.com
Oh-oh-oh
Hit me like a shot in the heart
Never shoulda played you so hard
Guess I played myself, that's my fault
Mmm-mm-mm
I don't even know how to think
'Cause now she got your
heart so I feel
Stupid, foolish
'Fraid I'm losing everything
I thought I couldn't
My whole world is falling apart
Don't you go falling in love
Trust me she's not the one
She won't ever
Love you like I do
Hold you like I do, know you like I do
Don't you go fallin' in love
'Cause I'ma break that shit up
I won't let her
Love you like I do
Touch you like I do, nothing like I do
Nothing like I do
Hit me like a poisonous dart
You wеre trouble right from the start
Should havе ran, I guess it's my fault
Mmm-mm-mm
I don't even know how to think
'Cause now she got your
heart so I feel
Stupid, foolish
'Fraid I'm losing everything
I thought I couldn't
My whole world is falling apart
Don't you go falling in love
Trust me she's not the one
She won't ever
Love you like I do
Hold you like I do, know you like I do
Don't you go fallin' in love
'Cause I'ma break that shit up
I won't let her
Love you like I do
Touch you like I do, nothing like I do
Nothing like I do
by RentAnAdviser.com